
export const html5 = [
    {
        "id": 1, "question": "what is Html ?", "Answer": `HTML : Hyper Test Markup Language.
            a)It is browser understandable language to display Information in Browser.
            b)It is Collection of Elements.
            c)The Information Transvers through the HTTP protocal.
            It has 2 main parts/sections those are 
            1)Head : It has Non-visuiable elements 
            2)Body : It has Visiable elements.
        `},
    {
        "id": 2, "question": "What is Role of !DOCtype ?",
        "Answer": `HTML is DOCTYPE. 
            Which means the document which has extension of .html
             then the browser understand that document is HTML Document and execute it.
            `
    },
    {
        "id": 3, "question": "What are the Tags and Element in HTML?",
        "Answer": `The Element in between the fragment is called as Tag. Tags are two type those are 
            1)Tag with opening and closing
            2)Tag with self closing
            Element denotes the Scope of the Content/text. Elements are the 2 types 
            1)Block level Elements: Which tags are starts from new line. Ex: div 
            2)Inline Elements :Which tags are starts in Same line. Ex: span
            `
    },
    {
        "id": 4, "question": "Use of title and meta tag in html?",
        "Answer": `Those two tags are in the Head section. Those are used to denote/shown 
            in the browser title bar. Meta provides the information about the Document.
            Display a title for page in search Engine Result.            
            `
    },
    {
        "id": 5, "question": "What is the empty tags in Html?",
        "Answer": `Which tags are not having any content to display ,
             but perform some action on pages those are called the empty tags.
            Example: <br/>,<hr/>,<Strong>,<b> …….ect             
            `
    },
    {
        "id": 6, "question": "The Difference between div and span tag?",
        "Answer": `div is block level element. Div Tag always starts from new line.
            it acts as container span is inline element. Span tag starts in same line                  
            `
    },
    {
        "id": 7, "question": "What are the sematic elements in Html?",
        "Answer": `HTML5 Interduce the new kind of tags those are called sematic tags.
            Those are nav, header, aside, address, section, footer                              
            `
    },
    {
        "id": 8, "question": "What is An Attribute?",
        "Answer": `An Additional information provides to the Element is called Attribute.
            Thore are 3 predefine Attributes 1)general 2)class 3)id                              
            `
    },
    {
        "id": 9, "question": "What are the content models in HTML?",
        "Answer": `There are 7 type of content model.
            1)Meta Data
            2)Embed
            3)Sectioning
            4)Interaction
            5)headers
            6)Flow
            7)phrasing                                          
            `
    },
    {
        "id": 10, "question": "can we write the HTML tags in Uppercase?",
        "Answer": `yes. We can Write in uppercase..                                          
            `
    },
    {
        "id": 11, "question": "General Syntex of Html",
        "Answer": `<!DOCTYPE html>
            <html>
               <head>
                    <title>Document</title> 
                </head>
                <body>
		            <h1>Basic Layout page</h1>
                </body>
            </html>                                        
            `
    },
]